|     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|  | » [News](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=news "News") \| [Download](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=download "Download") \| [Change log](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=changelog "Change log") \| [Screenshots](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=screenshots "Screenshots") \| [Guides](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=guides "Guides") \| [Forum](https://forum.imgburn.com/ "Forum") \| [Reviews](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=reviews "Reviews") \| [Links](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=links "Links") |  |

|     |
| --- |
|  |
|     |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|  |  |  |

|     |
| --- |
| Info |
| Current version: 2.5.8.0  <br>Released: 16th June 2013 |

|     |
| --- |
| Donate |
| Help me improve  <br>ImgBurn  <br>  <br>[](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&hosted_button_id=WHV49WMXAPFEC)  <br>[")](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&hosted_button_id=WHV49WMXAPFEC)[")](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&hosted_button_id=BMREHYBJHWHCG)[")](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&hosted_button_id=NZ2T836QPRU5U) |

|     |
| --- |
|     |
| advertisement |

|     |
| --- |
| Hosted By |

|     |
| --- |
| Awards |
| [](https://fileforum.betanews.com/detail/ImgBurn/1128426215/1)  <br>[](https://www.majorgeeks.com/files/details/imgburn.html)  <br>[](https://www.softpedia.com/get/CD-DVD-Tools/Data-CD-DVD-Burning/ImgBurn.shtml) |

|     |
| --- |
| Social Networking |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|  |  |  |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|  | » Privacy Policy |  |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Privacy Policy |     | [](#top) |

Last Modified: May 13th, 2018  
  
We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the website imgburn.com. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.  
  
This policy will let you know:

1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you
2. What cookies are and how they are used
3. How your information is used
4. Who is collecting your information
5. Special Google AdSense Notification for imgburn.com
6. Special Google Analytics Notification for imgburn.com
7. With whom your information may be shared
8. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information
9. How you can access, update or delete your information
10. The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
11. What else you should know about your online privacy

**What personally identifiable information does this site collect from me?**

We endeavour to collect as little personally identifiable information as possible. However, use of the online forum on our site requires the disclosure of some personal information when you register. During registration you are asked for your email address.  
  
Wherever we collect personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

**What are cookies and how does this site use them?**

As part of offering and providing customisable and personalised services, the site uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. All sites on imgburn.com where you are prompted to login or that are customisable require that you accept cookies. (See "What are my choices regarding collection, use and distribution of my information?" for more information on cookies.)  
  
We may use [third-party advertising companies](https://d3tciw3e8t1d98.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website.  
  
We use Google AdSense on this website. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your website visits. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on your web browsing activity. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [https://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads/](https://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads/)  
  
We use Google Analytics on this website. Google Analytics generates statistical information about website use by means of cookies. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/)  
  
We use IP.Board forum software from IPS, Inc. on this website. Using cookies is optional, but strongly recommended. Cookies are used to keep track of many various bits of information on the board, including automatically logging you in when returning to the board.  
  
We use Social Networking plug-ins on this website. The plug-ins may create cookies when you 'Like' (Facebook) or 'Follow' (Twitter) us.  
  
Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking 'Tools', 'Internet Options', 'Privacy', and selecting 'Block all cookies' using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including ours.

**How does this site use my information?**

We currently do not utilise, parse, or analyse any personally identifiable information gathered on imgburn.com. We reserve the right to change this behaviour and use of information in the future in order to provide you, the user, with a customised browsing experience. This includes personalisation services, interactive communications, and many other types of services, all of which are completely free to you. In order to provide services free of charge, we may display advertisements. By knowing a little about you, we are able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content, and hence better service, to you.

**Who is collecting information?**

When you are using this site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with this site alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than us, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service.  
  
Please be aware that advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to imgburn.com are not covered by this privacy statement.

**Special Google AdSense Notification for imgburn.com**

In this usage policy, the AdSense usage disclaimer has been added by the recommendation of Google, which serves ads on imgburn.com through its AdSense program.  
  
When you visit imgburn.com and click an advertisement syndicated by Google, a cookie (DoubleClick DART Cookie) is automatically added to your browser to help Google deliver you more targeted and useful ads.  
  
If you do not wish to get the cookie on your browser, you can visit Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
  
This is done in accordance with the Google AdSense policies, Google AdSense terms and conditions, and the latest notification of changes in Google's official Inside AdSense blog [here](https://adsense.blogspot.co.uk/).

**Special Google Analytics Notification for imgburn.com**

"This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the USA. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above."

**With whom do you share my information?**

As a general rule, we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under court order or subpoena.  
  
We may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms and Conditions of Use or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

**What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?**

You have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those imgburn.com Services that require registration in order to participate.  
  
We do not sell or rent user information to anyone. We will notify you at the time of data collection or transfer if your data will be shared with a third party and you will always have the option of not permitting the transfer. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service or not to participate in certain promotions or contests.

**What is your policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally identifiable information?**

You may edit your account information at any time by using your User ID and password.

**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**

Your account information is password protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. You may edit your account information by using your User ID and password.  
  
We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.  
  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

**What else should I know about my privacy?**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  
  
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

**Additional Information**

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to contact@imgburn.com

**Notification of changes**

Please be aware that by visiting this site or using imgburn.com Services, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes within this page so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also read the Terms of Service establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Site, the Services and application.

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|  |  |  |

|     |     |     |     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
|  |  | Copyright � 2005 - 2021 LIGHTNING UK! |  | [](#top) |  |  |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
|  | [Privacy Policy](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=privacy "Privacy Policy") \| [Terms and Conditions](https://www.imgburn.com/index.php?act=terms "Terms and Conditions") |  |
